{
    "exam_name": "C Programming Set 9",
    "total_marks": 20,
    "time_limit": 20,
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x - (x > 2 ? x : -x));<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "3",
                "B": "-3",
                "C": "0",
                "D": "5"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of x after the following code?<br><br><pre>int x = 5;<br>x = x + x-- - x++;</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "5",
                "B": "4",
                "C": "1",
                "D": "0",
                "E": "Undefined behavior"
            },
            "correct_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 7;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x & -x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "1",
                "C": "7",
                "D": "-7"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 10;<br>    int y = 5;<br>    x ^= x ^ y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "10",
                "B": "5",
                "C": "15",
                "D": "0"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    x += y-- + ++x;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "8",
                "B": "9",
                "C": "7",
                "D": "6"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 2;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    int z = x++ + ++y - x++;<br>    printf(\"%d\", z);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "3",
                "D": "4"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 2;<br>    x *= y + 2;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "14",
                "B": "15",
                "C": "12",
                "D": "10"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 7;<br>    int y = 2;<br>    int z = (x &= y) || (y += x);<br>    printf(\"%d\", z);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "1",
                "C": "2",
                "D": "7"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 2;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    x = (x + 1) * (y++);<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "6",
                "B": "9",
                "C": "10",
                "D": "8"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 10;<br>    int y = 5;<br>    x = x / y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "1",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "5",
                "D": "10"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 10;<br>    int y = 5;<br>    x = x / (y - 5);<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "1",
                "C": "5",
                "D": "10"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 10;<br>    int z = x && y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", z);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "1",
                "C": "5",
                "D": "10"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 10;<br>    int y = 5;<br>    int z = x || y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", z);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "1",
                "C": "5",
                "D": "10"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 10;<br>    x += x + (y--, x++);<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "16",
                "B": "15",
                "C": "14",
                "D": "13"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    int z = x++ - --y + x++;<br>    printf(\"%d\", z);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "6",
                "B": "7",
                "C": "4",
                "D": "5"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 3;<br>    int y = 7;<br>    x = x | y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "3",
                "B": "7",
                "C": "10",
                "D": "4"
            },
            "correct_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    x ^= x & y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "3",
                "D": "5"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 3;<br>    int y = 7;<br>    x = (x & y) << 1;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "0",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "3",
                "D": "6"
            },
            "correct_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 5;<br>    int y = 3;<br>    x = x - y++ * x;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "15",
                "B": "10",
                "C": "0",
                "D": "5"
            },
            "correct_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?<br><br><pre>void main() {<br>    int x = 7;<br>    int y = 2;<br>    x |= y;<br>    printf(\"%d\", x);<br>}</pre>",
            "options": {
                "A": "7",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "0",
                "D": "9"
            },
            "correct_answer": "D"
        }
    ]
}
